etemaaddaily.com 2018-12-24

# Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting **Etemaaddaily.com** , the website of **The Etemaad Urdu Daily, Hyderabad**. We respect your privacy and consider it an important element of our business. Our privacy policy is straightforward: We do not collect personal information about you when you visit our website(s) unless you volunteer to provide that information to us. 

The kind of information that is gathered automatically include the type of browser you are using (eg: Google Chrome, Firefox, Internet Explorer etc.), the type of Operating System you are using (eg: Windows 7, 8 , 10 , Mac) and the domain name of your Internet Service Provider (eg. BSNL,VSNL), the date and time of your visit and the pages you visit. We sometimes use this non-personally identifiable information to improve our website(s) design, content and primarily to give you a better browsing experience.

 **Personal Information Collected**

We collect personal information from you only if you provide it voluntarily. The type of personally identifiable information that may be collected by us include name, address, e-mail address and information about your interests in and use of various services. For example, you might submit your name and e-mail address to subscribe to our newsletters or to take part in our discussion forum or to send us your feedback.

 **Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites and Sponsors**

Our website(s) sometimes contain links to other websites whose privacy policies may be different to ours. Visitors should consult the other sites’ privacy notices as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.

 **Links to Other Sites**

Our website(s) has links to other website(s) in the World Wide Web. The privacy policies of these website(s) is not under our control. Once you leave our servers, use of any information you provide is governed by the privacy policy of the operator of the site you are visiting. It is advisable to read their privacy policies for further information.

 **Changes in this Privacy Statement**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement and such other places we deem appropriate so that you are updated about the manner we collect information, what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently

 **Contact Us**

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us
